<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecycleView</string>

    <string-array name="provinces">
        <item></item>
        <item>Munster</item>
        <item>Leinster</item>
        <item>Connacht</item>
        <item>Ulster</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="description">
        <item></item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="munster">
        <item></item>
        <item>Cork</item>
        <item>Kerry</item>
        <item>Waterford</item>
        <item>Tipperary</item>
        <item>Limerick</item>
        <item>Clare</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="munster_description">
        <item></item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cork">
        <item></item>
        <item>Garnish Island</item>
        <item>Lough Hyne</item>
        <item>Doneraile Park</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cork_description">
        <item></item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
        <item>Lovely Place</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction">
        <item>Garnish Island</item>
        <item>Lough Hyne</item>
        <item>Doneraile Park</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="visitorinfo">

        <item>Garnish Island, is an island in Glengarriff harbour, part of Bantry Bay in southwest Ireland.
The garden, designed by Harold Peto, is renowned for its gardens and architecture. The gardens extend over 37 acres and its
structures include a clock tower, a Grecian temple, a Matello Tower, and an Italian casita.</item>

        <item>Lough Hyne is a fully marine sea lough in West Cork, Ireland, about 5 km southwest of
Skibbereen. It was designated as Irelands first Marine Nature Reserve in 1981. The lakes small size, creates an unusual
habitat of highly oxygenated yet warm seawater that sustains an enormous variety of plants and animals.</item>

        <item>The Park comprises approximately 166 hectares and is an outstanding
example of an 18th century landscaped park in the Capability Brown style.
Mature groves of deciduous trees, several restored water features and a number of deer herds
can be viewed along the many pathways within the Park. The pathways are generally accessible for people with special needs.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="todoinfo">

        <item>Visitors to Garnish Island, situated in the harbour of Glengarriff in Bantry Bay, Co. Cork can view some of the
most spectacular and beautiful scenery the country has to offer by booking a fair through one of several ferry services available.
These affordable ferries generally include a tour of the nearby seal colony, before arriving at the famous gardens.</item>

        <item>Visitors can exhibition on the lough, where gain further information into its
importance by visiting the nearby Skibbereen Heritage Centre. There are also many more sites to see, with the
ruins of Saint Bridgits Church are on the shores of the lake, as well as holy wells, Tobarín Súl and Skour Well,
on the side of Knockomagh Hill. Castle Island is located in the center of the lake where the ruins of Cloghan Castle,
once a fortress of the O Driscoll clan, are still visible. A nature trail up Knockomagh Hill offers superb views of the
lough and the surrounding area.</item>

        <item>Doneraile Court, the former residence of the St. Leger family,
is situated within the Park. It is opened to the public following completion of restoration
works, there is a Tea Rooms onsite (open 7 days a week) and New Large Childrens Playground.
There are a number of free guided tours throughout the year.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recommendinfo">
        <item>Perfect for couples looking to spend a day out together, as well as nature lovers who
will love the unique green gardens and animal lovers who can pose for photos with the seal colony.</item>

        <item>Lough Hyne is a beautiful place for visitors who like to kayak and swim.
It is also perfect for those looking to get out for some exercise, who can embark on a lovely 7Km level walk.</item>

        <item>Perfect attraction for those looking for a family day out, peaceful and pleasant for the adults,
with a great playground for the kids as well as plenty of ducks and swans.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_destination">
        <item>Garnish Island</item>
        <item>Lough Hyne</item>
        <item>Doneraile Park</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>